

THƯ XIN THỰC TẬP

Vị trí: Thực tập sinh phòng quản lý sản phẩm

Kính gởi: Phòng Nhân Sự - Công ty Dược phẩm Bayer Việt Nam

Em là Trần Quốc Hùng, tốt nghiệp ngành Dược năm 2016 tại trường Đại học Y Dược Huế. Hiện tại em đang là học viên cao học cùa chương trình The Master Mekong Pharma 2018, chuyên ngành Quản lý chất thuốc do trường Đại học Paris Descartes liên kết với trường Đại học Dược Hà Nội đào tạo. Với mong muốn được có cơ hội tiếp xúc và thực tập tại vị trí thực tập sinh phòng quản lý sản phẩm của công ty. Em viết thư này kính mong nhận được sự đồng ý của công ty cho kỳ thực tập kéo dài 6 tháng sắp tới của khóa học (tháng 2 – tháng 8/2019).

Với niềm yêu thích và khả năng của mình, năm 2016 em đã lựa chọn và hoàn thành khóa luận tốt nghiệp về lĩnh vực bào chế, đó là khoảng thời gian em được tìm hiểu chuyên sâu về quy trình để hoàn thiện một sản phẩm, các tá dược, kỹ thuật trong bào chế, kiểm nghiệm và cách để xây dưng tiêu chuẩn chất lượng cho sản phẩm của mình. Hiện tại em đang công tác giảng dạy tại trường Cao đẳng y tế Lâm Đồng, qua 2 năm công tác em luôn cố gắng trau dồi thêm các kỹ năng về giảng dạy và tiếp tục cũng cố kiến thức chuyên môn của mình để đảm nhận công tác đào tạo được tốt hơn. Đó cũng chính là nguồn động lực giúp em theo đuổi và phấn đầu để được nhận vào chương trình MMP nơi mà em được đào tạo những kiến thức, kỹ năng chuyên sâu trong lĩnh vực quản lý chất lượng thuốc.

Vì vậy em tin rằng với những kiến thức, kỹ năng và kinh nghiệm của mình em có thể nhanh chóng tiếp cận, phối hợp và hỗ trợ các hoạt động của công ty. Em hy vọng sẽ nhận được hồi âm của công ty cho một buổi phỏng vấn trong thời gian sắp tới để em có thể trình bày cụ thể hơn về khả năng của mình. Em xin chân thành cám ơn quý công ty đã dành thời gian cho hồ sơ này

Trần Quốc Hùng



APPLICATION FOR INTERNSHIP

Position: Product specialist

Dear: Department of Human resources – Bayer Vietnam

My name is Tran Quoc Hung, I graduated from Hue University of Medicine and Pharmacy with a Bachelor degree of in July 2016. I am currently a graduate student of the Master Mekong Pharma 2018 program specializing in: Quality of medicine offered by the University of Paris Descartes affiliated training with the Hanoi University of Pharmacy. With the desire of being given an opportunity to practice in the professional and modern environment of the company, I write this letter with the expectation of receiving the company's approval for the next 6 month-internship of the course (February - August 2019).

In my final year at universities, I chose doing graduation thesis in the field of pharmaceutical manufacturing. That was such a valuable time for me to learn and practice more about: excipients and techniques and processes to make product, pathways to build quality standards for products and finally quality control of drugs. And now, during two- year working as a lecturer at Lam Dong medical college, I have always tried to improve not only my teaching skills but also my professional knowledge so that I can take my responsibility in the best way. This is also an intense motivation for me applying The Master Mekong Pharma program where I will be trained in both knowledge and skills in the field of quality of medication.

With knowledge, skills and experience I have accumulated, I believe that I can quickly approach to new things, coordinate with other related departments and can support activities. I am looking forward to hear from you soon and hope to have an interview so that I can express more about myself.

Trần Quốc Hùng



Contact me

- +84 966 999 063
- 0
- 973, QL 20, Liên Nghĩa, Đức Trọng Lâm Đồng, Việt Nam

trancanh17@gmail.com

f

Gt Trần Quốc Hùng

References

Assoc. Prof. Nguyen Thi Hoai

- Dean of Faculty of Pharmacy
- Hue University of Medicine and Pharmacy, Hue, Viet Nam
- Email: hoai77@gmail.com

Mrs. Florence DELCHER:

- Project manager ASIA
- Fondation Pierre Fabre
- Email:

florence.delcher@fondationpierrefabre.org

Education

2018 - Now

- Student of Master MeKong Pharma 2018
- Training: Paris Descartes University
- Location: Hanoi University of Pharmacy
- Major: Quality of Medication

2011 - 2016

- Graduated from Hue University of Medcine and Pharmacy July 2016
- Major: Pharmacy
- Completed Graduation Thesis
- GPA: **8.35/10**

2008 - 2011

- Student of High School for the Gifted Vietnam National University Ho Chi Minh City
- Major: Physics

Award - Activities

2016 - Now

- Consolation prize at Vietnam National Vocational 2018
- Consolation prize at Vocational teacher at Lam Dong provincial level 2018.
- Certificate in Healthcare Management Hospital
 Management of Hanoi Medical University Institute for
 Preventive and Public Health
- Certificate in Medical Education of Hanoi Medical
 University Institute for Preventive and Public Health

2011 - 2016

- First prize at "Conference on Student Scientific Research" held at Hue University of Medicine and Pharmacy 2016
- Awards given for "Good student and actively participate in the activities of the school" for 5 years
- First prize at "Design Logo for Nhịp Cầu Dược Lâm Sàng Facebook"

2008 - 2011

- Scholarship LAWRENCE S. TING Phu My Hung
- First prize at "Micom Car Rally" held by University Of Science Ho Chi Minh Viet Nam in 2009, 2010

English

TOEIC (R+L): 710 (10/2017)

Thank Sir/Madam for spending time reading my CV

Work experience

2018 - Now

Student of Master MeKong Pharma 2018

- Industrial development of the drug
- Good manufacturing / distribution practices
- Application of instrumental methods
- Quality of raw materials
- Analytical development and control of active substances

09/2016 - Now

Lecturer at Lam Dong Medical College

- Department of Pharmaceutical
- Participate in scientific research at Biological Research Center - Lam Dong Medical College
- Workig as main member in research "Formulation and evaluation of herb sedative tea bag" at Lam Dong Medical College.
 - + Quality control herbal material
 - + Formulate ingredients for tea bag product
- + Establishing quality standards for tea bag products

6/2015 - 6/2016

Student - Completing Thesis

- Thesis title: "Formulation of a moisturizing cream containing quercetin"
 - Formulate ingredient for cosmetic product
 - Establish quality standards for ointment product.
 - Experience on ointment quality control.
 - Clinical trial: Anti-UV test on mice:

Computer



Skill

- Independent work
- Team work
 - Communication
- Presentation
- Problem-solving

